I'm sorry.
なお (菜緒)ごめん
Thank you.
ありがとう
This is good.
おいしい
Here.
(大地)ん...
My mom gave these to me.
おふくろがくれた
It's good.
おいしい
She only bought this because she wants to eat them.
自分が食べたいから 買ってきたんだろうな
This is so sweet.
甘い
You don't like sweets much, do you, Daichi?
大ちゃん 甘いの苦手だもんね
But you gave me chocolates every year.
でも毎年 菜緒はチョコくれる
That's because if I give you ones that I want to eat
自分が食べたいのを買って 渡せば
then I can eat them with you.
緒に食べれるもんね
I think you ate most of them.
ほとんど とってたもんな お前が食
Daichi.
大ちゃん
Today, I--
FAta...
Don't worry. It's OK.
(大地)いいよ別に
If you don't want to talk about it, then don't.
話したくないことは 話さないで
You can stay here tonight if you want to.
(大地)今日泊まってっても いいんだぞ
We've got school tomorrow...
明日学校あるし
so I'll go back home today.
今日は帰るね
Yuri... how are you feeling?
(卓也)百合体調は?
I heard you have a fever.
熱あるって
I thought you were coming home late tonight.
佰刽 今日は遅くなるんじゃなかったの?
Listen to me, Yuri.
百合聞いてくれ
I'm feeling tired.
ダルい
-So we can have dinner out, OK? -I want to tell you everything.
夕飯外食でいいよね? (卓也)本当のこと話すよ
I'd like to have soba or something.
あー私 おソバとか食べたい あお
-Come on, listen. -I don't want to hear it!
(卓也)ねえ聞いて 佰刽聞きたくない!
Hear him out.
うえはら (上原)聞いてやれば?
You can still divorce him after you listen to what he has to say.
別れるのは話聞いてからでも 遅くないだろ
You stay out of this!
お前は黙ってろ!
Sorry for not telling you about my transfer.
転勤のこと 黙ってて悪かった
I meant to tell you all about it.
ちゃんと話すつもりだったんだ こつにんに
-Yeah, right. -I did. I'm serious.
どうだか (卓也)本当だよ
How can you talk to your ex-girlfriend...
元カノに相談できて
but not talk to me about it?
私に話せないって どうし)うこと?
Her husband was transferred to live alone overseas,
彼女の旦那さんが 海外に単身赴任してて
so I wanted to ask her some questions about it.
いろいろと相談に 乗ってもらってたんだ つつてたん
So? What if her husband is overseas?
ふーん 旦那さん海外なんだ
She really has nothing to do with this. I just...
彼女は関係ない本当に ただ…
I just couldn't tell you, that's all.
俺がただ言えなかっただけ こに言えなかったに
Couldn't tell me what?
何をよ
I want you to come with me.
ついてきてくれって
I know what you'd say.
分かってたんだ
You'd say that you'd throw away your life here
百合は今の生活全部捨てて
and come with me.
ついてくって 言ってくれるって
-Then why-- -But if you did...
だったら、 こつたら… 倬也)そうなったら!
If you did... you wouldn't be losing just your job...
そうなったら 今の仕事だけじゃなくて
but our home in Japan too.
日本の俺たちの家も なくなるんだ
Don't tell me...
(上原)お前もしかして
you were worried about me having a place to stay.
俺が帰る場所なくなるとか 心配してんの?
I never asked you to do that.
余計なお世話だから
Or maybe
それとも何?
you were going to let me have Yuri?
百合を俺に 譲る気になったってこと?
I knew it. You and your ex-girlfriend are getting on good.
やっぱ元カノと いい感じになっちゃったんだ
It only makes sense.
そりゃそうだよな
Instead of this crazy drunk,
こんな酒癖の悪い女より
you'd rather be with a woman that understands your work--
仕事に理解のある女のほうが いいよな
-What did you do-- -I told you before.
何すんだよ 倬也)言っただろ
I will never let you have Yuri.
百合だけは譲れない
Then take her with you!
だったら連れてけよ!
If we go there,
倬也向こうに行ったら 3年は帰ってこれなくなる
You'll have to quit your current job,
今の仕事も 辞めてもらわなきゃいけないし
and we won't be able to see Hisashi.
ひさし 久志にも会えなくなる
You already know, right?
分かってるんでしょ?
You know what I'll say.
私が何て言うか
Oh, sorry.
あっごめん
Uehara.
久志
Sorry about the trouble I caused you.
あ…悪かったな 迷惑かけて
Quit being a pussyfoot!
フラフラしてんじゃねえよ
That's payback.
さっきのお返し
Nao.
菜緒ちゃん
So that means Yuri stayed overnight here?
ゆりりん 泊まってたってこと?
UNKNOWN
(スマホのパイプ音)
Hello. This is Yoshikawa Nao.
はい吉川です
-Nao. -Uhm, Uehara...
吉川 (菜緒)あのね上原君
I just found out there's an opening at the girls' dorm from next month.
来月から女子寮の空き 出るんだって こつ
What?
仩原)え?
They said I could move right in at that time.
そしたらすぐ 入寮していいって
I didn't expect an opening this soon.
こんな早く空くとはね
Oh, I see.
(上原)そっか
That's good news.
よかったな
It's a little sooner than I planned, but it's OK, right?
予定より少し早いけど 大丈夫だよね
Nao,
上原)吉川 仩原)吉川
-about today-- -Sorry...
今 日 (菜緒)ごめん!
but I don't want to hear about it.
聞きたくない
I'm going to sleep for a while.
私ちょっと寝るね
Oh!
(まりな)あっ
Good morning!
おはよう!
-Oh, Marina. -Good morning.
あつまりな (光石)おはよう
Good morning.
おはよう
So, how was your Valentine's date?
でどうだったの? バレンタインデートは
Did you tell him?
ちゃんと伝えた?
No.
ううん
What? You mean you didn't tell him?
え?何?言わなかったの?
No, it was kind of...
うんちょっとね
Jeez! You look so depressed.
何だよ暗い顔して
-Mitsuishi, you go on ahead. -Huh? Why?
みつちゃん先行ってて 侊司うーんいや
-Dang, you're cold. -Just go!
冷たいなお前も (まりな)いいから
-But we were so lovey-dovey yester-- -Mitsuishi!
(光石)昨日あんなに ラブラブしてたのにさ
OK.
(光石)はい
Nao?
菜緒?
Yuri, huh?
(まりな)ゆりりんか
You know, there may have been a good reason for it.
何か事情があったのかも つに しれないよ?
Like what?
(菜緒)どんな?
Uh, well... Look,
あつそれは...ほら
when a friend is truly in trouble,
友達が本当に困ってたら
you'd at least want to listen to their problem, right?
話聞いてあげようぐらい 思うもんじゃん?
-But she's not a friend. -Huh?
(菜緒)友達じゃないじゃん (まりな)え?
Yuri's not just a friend.
ゆりりんは 友達じゃないじゃん
I mean, he's always liked her.
だって ずっと好きだった人だよ
But, even though he used to like her, she's still his sister-in-law.
でもさ好きだった人をさ 一応お姉さんだし
You wouldn't like it if he were the type of guy
それを無視しちゃうような
who was cold and ignored that kind of thing.
冷たい人のほうが イヤじゃない?
Yeah.
うん
But...
でも...
what I hate more is seeing Uehara become all frantic over Yuri.
ゆりりんのことで 必死になってる
I hate myself for hating Yuri too.
ゆりりんのこと恨んじゃう 自分もイヤだし
And I really hate myself for being so jealous.
ヤキモチ焼く自分も大嫌い
I'm going all crazy inside!
もう何かグチャグチャだよ
Nao, why don't you stay at my place for a while?
菜緒さしばらく うちに泊まりおいでよ
I'll listen to you complain about whatever you like.
グチでも何でも聞くからさ
OK?
ねつ a
OK.
(菜緒) うん
What did you want to talk to me about?
(上原)何ですか?用って
What's your problem?
どういうつもりだよ
I thought you said you told Nao how you felt about her.
お前菜緒に気持ち 伝えたんじゃなかったのか?
Then how come she was crying?
なのに何で あいつが泣いてんだよ
She was soaking wet, carefully carrying that cake.
ずぶ濡れで 大事そうにケーキ抱えて
What's wrong with you?
どうなんだよ!
Are you even thinking about Nao's feelings?
お前菜緒の気持ち 考えてんのか
If you make a promise, then keep it!
約束したなら こなら ちゃんと守れよ!
You got her hopes up and played with her feelings.
期待だけさせて振り回して
She just giggles and brushes off whatever you say.
お前に何言われても ヘラヘラ笑ってる
Have you ever thought about her feelings?
あいつの気持ち 考えたことあんのか!
No. No way. I won't let you.
(大地)やっぱお前だけは無理
I won't let you have Nao.
菜緒はやれない
She's the only one who can decide that.
それはあいつが 決めることでしょ
I'm not going to back off either.
俺も引く気はないんで
It's a little late to be saying that.
今さら何言ってんだよ
I knew letting you two live together was a mistake.
やっぱり同居が 間違いだったんだ
There you are. Where's Nao's special lunch?
(阿部)おついた 吉川特製弁当は? 可-
Jeez!
(DEB) FI y
I thought I'd be able to get some leftovers.
せっかくおこぼれ もらおうと思ったのに
So, how was the cake?
で?チョコどうだった?
You got one from Nao, didn't you?
もらったんだろ? 吉川から
I totally thought I'd get something at least from Nao this year, but,
俺も今年こそは絶対 吉川からもらえると思ったのに
"This year, I'm only giving one to the person I'm serious about."
“ごめんねあべっち べつ 本命は1本って決めてるのって
That's what she told me.
宣言されちゃつたもんなあ
How was it? Was Nao's true-love cake good?
どうだうまかったのか? つに 吉川の本命チョコ
-Oh! -You can have it.
(阿部)おおつ (上原)やる
What? Really?
(阿部)えつマジで?
You haven't had any of it.
食ってないじゃん
Nao.
菜緒
Daichi.
大ちゃん
Do you have a little time right now?
菜緒今少し時間ある?
Sorry, but I've got work today.
ごめん今日バイトなんだ
I see.
そっか
Are you all right?
大丈夫か?
Yeah.
うん
Nao's going to be staying at my place from today.
菜緒今日から うちに泊まるんで
OK.
うん
Thank you, Daichi.
ありがとね大ちゃん
-Bye. -See you.
じゃ (大地)じゃあな
OK.
うん
What are all these?
何これ
They're presents from customers.
(徹平)ありがたいことに お客さんからだよ
-They're all for Issei? -Yep.
全部いっちゃん宛て? (一星)ふふん 小小 いっせい
I can't believe you're popular, Issei.
(菜緒) いっちゃんってモテるんだ
Hey, I'm called the "Handsome Manager," you know!
これでもイケメン店員って 呼ばれてんだぞ
-Really? -He takes after me.
(菜緒)え? (徹平)俺に似てな! え俺 菜︶
By the way, did you meet up with him yesterday?
ってか昨日 ちゃんとあいつと会えたのか?
-Huh? -Uh... Uehara, is that his name?
(菜緒)ん? (一星)あの…上原だっけ?
-He came here yesterday. -Really?
昨日店来たぞ (菜緒)え?
He was looking for you.
お前のこと捜しに
Sorry, but we're still closed.
あっすいません まだ準備中で
Aren't you Nao's...
ってお前吉川の
Has she been here?
あいつ来てませんか?
No, today's her day off.
ああ今日休みだけど
Yeah, I thought so.
そうですよね
Thanks.
すいません
He was kind of frantic.
(一星)何か慌てて
Did you give him the cake?
ちゃんとチョコ渡せたのか?
No.
ううん
I see.
そっか
So, you mean,
(まりな)上原君菜緒のこと 捜し回ってたってこと?
Yeah, I think so.
うんたぶん
Don't you think you should see him and talk about it?
ちゃんと会って話したほうが いいんじゃないの?
You can't keep avoiding him like this, you know.
このまま顔を合わせないなんて 無理なんだからさ
There's an opening in the girls' dorm.
女子寮にね空きができたの
Really?
え?
They said I can move in next month.
来月には入れるって
So you'd move out of your place?
あの家出るってこと?
I still haven't given an answer to the dorm.
寮にはまだ返事してないけど
But we already decided that we'd only live together
でも同居ももともと 寮が空くまでって話してたし
Besides, I can't keep it secret from my parents forever.
それに両親にずっと 内緒にしてるわけにはいかないし
Is that what you want?
それでいいの?
I don't know anymore.
もう分かんないよ
He told me that he likes me, but I don't know if it's true.
私のこと好きって言ったけど つに 本当なのかな
What?
(まりな)え?
It makes me think sometimes...
思うんだよね
what if it hadn't been me that was living with him?
一緒に住んでるのが 私じゃなかったらって… よかったらつ
It was just chance that I was close to Uehara.
たまたま上原君の近くに 私がいるだけで
But if I hadn't been,
そうじゃなかったら
then he probably wouldn't have even noticed me.
私のこと気にも とめてなかったんだろうなって
Then...
そしたら
I never would have had to go through falling in love with Uehara.
私も上原君のこと 好きにならなくて済んだのに
Nao.
(まりな)菜緒
And I never would have had to feel this way.
こんな思いしなくて 済んだのに
There's no point in talking like that now.
まりな)今さらそんなこと 言っても仕方ないじゃん
You've met, and that's that.
もう出会っちゃつたんだから つに
Listen to me.
あのね
Chance and fate and all that stuff,
偶然とか運命とか
that's what love is made of. All of it.
そういうの全部ひっくるめて 恋なの!
You could go on forever talking about "what-ifs."
"たられば”の話してたら キリがないよ
Has it really been nothing but heartbreak?
本当につらいこと ばっかりだった?
You were happy, Nao.
(まりな)菜緒笑ってたよ
You were happy when you fell in love with Uehara.
上原君好きになって笑ってた
I don't want you to regret falling in love with Uehara.
好きにならなきゃよかったなんて 思ってほしくない
OK.
うん
So, you need to tell Uehara
だから菜緒が思ってること
everything you're thinking about.
ちゃんと上原君に ぶつけてみなよ
Even if you do move into the dorm,
もし寮に入ることになっても
it's no good trying to run away from this.
このまま逃げるみたいなのは ダメだからね
OK.
うん
Oh! Answer it! Answer it! It might be Uehara.
あつ出て出て 上原君かもよ
Oh, it's Daichi.
大ちゃんか やんか.
Hello?
もしもし
Sorry about calling you so late.
ごめんな遅くに
It's OK.
ううん
What's wrong?
どうしたの?
You know, Nao, I still like you.
俺やっぱり菜緒のことが好き
If it were me, I'd never make you cry.
俺だったら こつたら 菜緒を泣かせたりしない
I'd never play with your feelings either.
振り回したりもしない
You know what I thought about when I saw you crying the other day?
こないだ泣いてる菜緒を見て 思ったんだ
I thought, "I want to be with Nao."
菜緒のそばにいてやりたいって
No, that's not it.
いや違うな
I want you to be with me.
そばにいてほしい
When I enter university, I'm thinking about living on my own.
俺大学入ったら 人暮らししようと思ってるんだ
Really? You're not going to commute from home?
え?実家から通うって
I changed my mind.
(大地)気が変わった
Nao, will you live with me?
休地) 菜緒一緒に暮らさない?
I want to live with you, Nao.
俺菜緒と暮らしたい
Daichi...
大ちゃん…
Nao.
菜緒
I want you to think it over carefully again.
もう一度 ちゃんと考えてほしい
Daichi...
大ちゃん
I...
de...
I think I might be moving out of there.
たぶんあの家出ると思う
Really?
え?
There's an opening at the girls' dorm.
女子寮にね空きができたの
They said I can move in next month.
来月から入れるって
-Then-- -But...
(大地)だったら こつたら (菜緒)でも つも だで 大︶
I'm sorry.
ごめん
I...
私…
I still like Uehara.
やっぱり 上原君のことが好きなの
With all my crying,
泣いてばっかで
I caused you a lot of trouble, Daichi.
大ちゃんにたくさん 迷惑かけちゃつたけど つに
But, I really still do like Uehara.
でもやっぱり 上原君のことが好き
No matter who he actually likes.
上原君が誰を好きでも
So...
(菜緒)だから
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
My second confession of love...
2度目の告白
and I get rejected again.
またフラれたな
Daichi.
大ちゃん
Well, I knew it would happen, though.
まあ分かってたけど
What's so great about that guy, anyway?
どこがいいんだよあんな奴
He's so selfish.
自分勝手だし
I can't tell what he's thinking at all.
何考えてるか 全然分かんないし かな
And he's mean,
意地悪だし
childish,
子供っぽいし
eats too much
大食いだし
and plays with my feelings all the time.
人の気持ち いっぱい振り回すし
But, still...
でもね
he's kind in a lot of ways too.
優しいところも いっぱいあるんだ
OK.
(大地) うん
This is delicious.
うまい
Ow, ow, ow!
(光石)痛い痛い痛い... もう何だよ
I'm supposed to be having lunch with Marina.
俺まりなと 弁当食わなきゃいけない…
There's nobody in there!
いねえよ
I feel like I could die if I don't tell someone this.
もう俺誰かに言わないと マジで死にそう
What?
何だよ
I felt like digging a hole and shouting into it.
もうさよっぽど 穴でも掘って
Daichi confessed his love to Nao.
大地先輩が吉川に告つてた
-That's old news. -You know about it?
(光石)いつの話してんだよ (阿部)知ってたの?
-Even though it happened yesterday? -Huh? Yesterday?
昨日のことなのに? (光石)ん?昨日?
Daichi said to Nao, "When I graduate, let's live together."
大地先輩"卒業したら 一緒に暮らそうって吉川に
Seriously? And what did Nao say?
マジかよ で菜緒は何て?
-Hey. -Before I could hear that,
(光石)おい (阿部)それ聞く前に
I ran away.
俺その場から逃げた
Why did you do that? Her answer's the important part!
何でだよ 重要なのそこだろお前
If Nao chose Daichi, what would happen to Uehara?
もし吉川が大地先輩選んだら 上原どうなるんだよ?
Uehara would be getting what he deserves.
上原君は自業自得だろ
He broke his Valentine's promise with Nao.
バレンタインの約束も すっぽかしたらしいし
-Really? -As for me,
(光石)俺は菜緒は え
But Uehara also likes Nao.
でも上原も 吉川のこと好きなんじゃ…
I'm not so sure about that.
(光石)そうかな?
It doesn't seem like he treats her very well.
菜緒のこと大事にしてるようには 思えないけど
Let's go, shall we?
(詩織) さあ行きましょ
I'm getting a really awful feeling about this.
何かすっごく マズい感じがする
-What? Seriously? -Yes, seriously.
(陽菜)えっマジ? 日 (エリカ)マジマジ
I heard Daichi asked Nao to live with him.
何か篠崎先輩が吉川菜緒に
So it's true about Daichi and Nao having that kind of relationship.
やっぱ篠崎先輩と吉川さんって そういう関係なの?
But don't you feel awful for Uehara?
(エリカ)ってか かわいそうじゃない?上原君
Yeah, the poor thing.
(陽菜)かわいそう本当に マジか~
-Oh, dear. -Uehara was right there.
(陽菜)ちょっと (エリカ)いたんだ上原君
Nao. Can we talk with you for a moment?
渼南) 吉川さんちょっといい?
OK.
うん
Is it true that you're going to live with Daichi when he graduates?
あんたさ卒業したら 篠崎先輩と同棲するって本当?
How do you know about that?
何で…
What are you talking about?
ちょっと何言ってんの?
We're not asking you, Marina--
(美南) 紺野さんには聞いてないし
You don't have to answer, Nao. This is so stupid.
(まりな)菜緒答えなくていいよ バカバカしい
It must be true if you can't deny it.
(エリカ)否定できないってことは 本当なんだ
It's quite a shock.
超びっくりなんだけど
So it was true that you have that kind of relationship with Daichi.
あなたやっぱり大地先輩と そういう関係だったのね
That means Uehara was just your toy, right?
(美南)上原君のことは 遊びだったってこと?
That poor Uehara.
かわいそう上原君
I would never--
そんな私は
-You're just sore that we found out. -That's right. Tell it to us straight!
(詩織)往生際の悪い人ね! (美南)そうよはっきりしなさいよ
You're going to choose Daichi, right?
大地先輩を選ぶのよね?
There's nothing to say. I just...
はっきりも何も ただ私は…
It was all my idea.
(大地) 俺が勝手に言ってるだけだよ
Daichi.
大ちゃん
We made it.
(光石)間に合った
Mitsuishi, you went and got him?
みつちゃん 呼んでくれたんだ
I was worried it would get out of hand.
収拾つかないと思ってさ
My love for her is all one-sided.
俺が勝手に 片思いしてるだけだから
Don't go bullying Nao for it.
菜緒のこと 責めないでくれる?
But...
(美南)でも
Nao!
(上原)吉川!
-Uehara!
(詩織,美南)上 君! 原
Come with me.
ちょっと来い
What do you want with her?
今さら何の用だよ?
-It's none of your business. -It's none of yours either.
関係ないでしょ (大地)お前も関係ないだろ
You broke up, didn't--
お前たち もう別れたんだろ?
We didn't break up!
別れてねーよ!
Let's go.
帰るぞ
That was on purpose, wasn't it, Daichi?
わざとでしょ大地先輩
Huh?
(大地)ん?
You got Uehara worked up on purpose, right?
わざと上原君 あおったでしょ? 君し 原で 上た とつ ざお わあ
I'm not as unselfish as that.
そんな心広くないけどな
You know, they really are a troublesome pair.
それにしても本当 世話の焼ける奴らだよな
You want to go out with us?
どっか行きます?
We'll go to karaoke or bowling, or anything you like.
カラオケボウリング 何でも付き合いますよ
-Abe will pay for everything. -Huh?
あべっちのおごりで (阿部)え?
He's the one who eavesdropped on you confessing your love.
こいつ先輩の告白 盗み聞きしてたんですよ
-Hey! -No, I wasn't.
(大地)おい (阿部)違います違います
I just happened to be there.
あれはたまたま
OK, let's go bowling after karaoke!
よし!じゃあ カラオケからのボウリング
We'll do it all!
フルコースで
-Are you serious? -Abe's paying.
(阿部)マジっすか (光石)おごり
Where did you stay last night?
(上原) どこ泊まりに行ってたんだよ
At Marina's place.
まりなんち
You mean, you were worried about me?
もしかして 気にしてくれてた?
No.
別に
I didn't think so.
だよね
It's got nothing to do with you.
関係ないもんね 上原君には…
I'm sorry.
ごめん
I'm sorry... I didn't keep my promise.
約束守れなくてごめん
There's nothing between Yuri and me.
俺百合とは何でもないよ
She was drunk
(上原)あいつ酔っ払って
and was staggering down the street in a terrible state.
どうしようもない状態で 街フラついてて
I couldn't help but look after her.
仕方なく面倒見ただけ
She came here only because she thought you were here.
あいつもお前がいると思って ここに来たし
She and my brother had a good talk and settled things.
兄貴とちゃんと話して 収まったよ つに
She was drunk.
(菜緒)酔っ払って 竿つ
Totally smashed... and threw up.
(上原)泥酔で吐かれて
Did she kiss you?
キスした?
Is that what you're worried about?
気にするのそこかよ
-I can't help it. -Don't be stupid.
だって… (上原)アホらしい アホらしい
That's no answer!
そんなの答えになってないよ!
-Where are you going? -I'm thirsty.
どこ行くんだよ (菜緒) ノド乾いたの!
What's this?
何これ
Isn't that what you said?
お前が言ったんだろ
You'd only want this in return.
お返しはそれがいいって
The cake... was delicious.
ケーキうまかった
But it was crushed.
潰れてたでしょ
It still tastes the same.
味は同じだろ
This isn't the kind of thing you're supposed to give as a present.
(菜緒) こういうの ホワイトデーに返すもんだよ
There are...
これ..
way too many.
多すぎだよ
Stay right here.
(上原) ここにいろ
Don't go anywhere.
どこも行くなよ
Uehara.
上原君
I like you.
き 好
I really like--
大好…
I know.
知ってる
OK.
うん
To all graduates and parents,
(校長)卒業生の皆さん ご父兄の皆様
I want to express my heartfelt congratulations.
本日は誠に おめでとうございます
Take a picture with me!
(女子生徒) 写真撮ってください
-Congratulations, Daichi!
(女子生徒)大地先輩 卒業おめでとうございます
-Picture, please. -Thank you.
(大地)ありがとう
-Here, here.
ありがとう
Daichi!
大ちゃん!
-Sorry. I have to go.
(大地) ごめんちょっと待って
-Daichi... -Sorry.
ごめんね
Excuse me.
ごめんなさい
Congratulations on graduating.
卒業おめでとう
Thank you.
ありがとう
Nao.
菜緒
When you've got tests, start studying ahead of time.
テストの時はちゃんと 前もって勉強しろよ
OK.
うん
And eat properly.
ちゃんと飯食えよ
And don't be late.
あと遅刻すんなよ
I know.
分かってる
And don't cry anymore.
(大地)もう泣くなよ
You know, I won't be around if you do.
泣いても俺もう 近くにいないからさ
OK.
うん
Daichi.
大ちゃん
Thank you.
ありがとう
Didn't I just tell you not to cry?
だからもう 泣くなって言ってんだろ!
I can't help it.
(菜緒)だって
Look who's here.
(大地)来たぞ
Nao!
(まりな)菜緒
Daichi, thanks for all you've done.
(光石)大地先輩 いろいろお世話になりました
Thank you.
(大地)サンキュ
-You can leave Nao in my hands. -What are you talking about?
吉川のことは任せてください (大地)お前何言ってんだよ
Well, you can leave Marina in my hands.
じゃあまりなのことは 俺に任せてください
-You got it. -Oh, Mitsuishi!
(大地)任せたぞ まりな)みつちゃん
I can't believe Daichi's graduating.
(まりな)大ちゃん卒業かあ
It was eight years.
(大地) 8年
My one-sided love for Nao was that long.
俺の菜緒への片思い
What are you laughing about?
(大地)何がおかしいんだよ
No... it's nothing.
(上原)いや別に
I totally thought forgetting was impossible.
忘れるの絶対無理って 思ってましたけど
But I was able to forget after meeting her.
俺あいつに会って 忘れられたんです
I was able to forget about someone I loved for eight years.
8年間想ってきた相手を
Are you encouraging me?
俺今励まされた?
Sorry if I sounded righteous.
上からですいません
That kind of pissed me off.
すげえムカつく
Uehara.
上原君
Let's go.
帰るぞ
OK.
うん
Dang, I'm hungry.
(上原)あー腹減った
Hey!
(菜緒)ちょっと
Huh? Ow!
え?痛いな
What do you want to eat today?
(上原)何食う?今日
Hey, quit walking away!
(菜緒) ちょっと何で逃げんのよ
-Come to think of it... -Huh?
(上原)そういえば (菜緒)ん?
-What happened with that? -With what?
(上原)あれどうなったんだよ
The girls' dorm.
(上原)女子寮
Oh, about that,
(菜緒) あーそのことなんだけど
I missed my chance to take it, so they got another person.
返事しそびれちゃつて 他の人に決まっちゃつたみたい
-Really? -But that's all right.
は ? (菜緒)でもいいんだ
You told me that you didn't want me to go anywhere.
上原君がどこにも行くなって 言ってくれたから
What?
仩原)はあ?
-You said that, right? -No, I didn't.
言ったでしょ (上原)言ってねえよ
Yes, you did!
言ったよ!
"Stay right here."
ここにいろよ"
-You're getting carried away. -Are you glad?
(上原)お前調子に乗んな (菜緒) うれしい?
Are you?
ねえ?
Not really.
別に
You can't be honest, can you?
素直じゃないんだ フフッ
What do you want for dinner tonight?
(菜緒)今日夕飯 何食べたい?
-Meat. -What? Meat again?
仩原)肉 (菜緒)えっまた肉? )ノ)ノ 上菜
-OK, braised beef and potato is fine. -But that's meat too!
じゃあ肉じゃがでもいいよ (菜緒)いやそれも肉だってば
Shabu-shabu would be nice.
しゃぶしゃぶでもいいけどね
And that's meat as well.
それも肉だけどね
Dad! Mom!
お父さんお母さん